Guide to the Collins Land Company (Helena, Mont.) Records 1898-1951
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Case Files, 1907-1951; Series II; 28.5 linear feet
  - Sequence 2, Subseries 2; 9.0 linear feet
    - Parrish, William M., Glasgow, Montana, Case Number 1453 (Box-folder 52/15)
    - Lohrer, Albert, Corbin, Montana, Case Number 1458 (Box-folder 53/1)
    - Neild, W. D., Townsend, Montana, Case Number 1467 (Box-folder 53/2)
    - Maclay, David R., Lolo, Montana, Case Number 1476 (Box-folder 53/3)
    - Barker-Wilson Company, Butte, Montana, Case Number 1532 (Box-folder 53/4)
    - Carson, Mary Carter, Butte, Montana, Case Number 1540 (Box-folder 53/5)
    - Patterson, J. Orville, Fort Benton, Montana, Case Number 1549 (Box-folder 53/6)
    - Valier-Montana Land and Water Company, Valier, Montana, Case Number 1554 (Box-folder 53/7)
    - Barker-Wilson Company, Butte, Montana, Case Number 1660 (Box-folder 53/8)
    - Hedrick, J. G., Halley, Idaho, Case Number 1672 (Box-folder 53/9)
    - Freeman, George D., Halley, Idaho, Case Number 1700 (Box-folder 53/10)
    - Whitbread, Fred, Hinsdale, Montana, Case Number 1813 (Box-folder 53/11)
    - Buck, John F., Capitol, Montana, Case Number 1814 (Box-folder 53/12)
    - Harris, W. E., Miles City, Montana, Case Number 1820 (Box-folder 53/13)
    - Gordon, William, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 1829 (Box-folder 53/14)
    - Colorado Rights, Case Number 1874 (Box-folder 53/15)
    - Blackstone, D. L., Chinook, Montana, Case Number 1933 (Box-folder 53/16)
    - Sprinkle, Charles E., Chinook, Montana, Case Number 2070 (Box-folder 53/17)
    - Big Hole Herding Association, Dillon, Montana, Case Number 2078 (Box-folder 53/18)
    - Shaw, George N., (Mrs.), Helena, Montana, Case Number 2107 (Box-folder 53/19)
    - Cornell, Craig, Dillon, Montana, Case Number 2719 (Box-folder 53/20)
  - Sequence 3, Subseries 3; 11.5 linear feet
    - Lindsay, Charles A., Butte, Montana, Case Number 2 (Box-folder 54/1)
    - J. B. Long and Company, Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 4 (Box-folder 54/2)
    - Ramsey, George L., Helena, Montana, Case Number 12 (Box-folder 54/3)
    - Allison, Perry, Morrhead, Montana, Case Number 13 (Box-folder 54/4)
    - Harris, W. E., Miles City, Montana, Case Number 16 (Box-folder 54/5)
    - Miller, Herman J., Glasgow, Montana, Case Number 17 (Box-folder 54/6)
    - Mariner, William J., Blalock, Oregon, Case Number 18 (Box-folder 54/7)
    - Selway, T. M., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 22 (Box-folder 54/8)
    - Thomas, William E. and Evan E., Madison County, Montana, Case Number 23 (Box-folder 54/9)
    - Holmer-Flagler Livestock Company, Fort Benton, Montana, Case Number 25 (Box-folder 54/10)
    - Simon, Nat, Butte, Montana, Case Number 28 (Box-folder 54/11)
    - Badger, B. W., White Sulphur Springs, Montana, Case Number 29 (Box-folder 54/12)
    - Nickel, Charles H., Butte, Montana, Case Number 30 (Box-folder 54/13)
    - Larrabee, Charles X., Home Park, Montana, Case Number 31 (Box-folder 54/14)
    - Dingwall, William, New Chicago, Montana, Case Number 33 (Box-folder 54/15)
    - Long, J. B., Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 40 (Box-folder 54/16)
    - Jones, Thomas A., Glasgow, Montana, Case Number 43 (Box-folder 54/17)
    - Grosfield, Abraham M., Big Timber, Montana, Case Number 44 (Box-folder 54/18)
    - Price, L. J. and Maurer, Christian W., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 46 (Box-folder 54/19)
    - First National Bank, Cody, Wyoming, Case Number 50 (Box-folder 54/20)
    - Milner, M. E., Fort Benton, Montana, Case Number 51 (Box-folder 54/21)
    - Hilger and Busenburg, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 56 (Box-folder 54/22)
    - Pepin, Simon, Havre, Montana, Case Number 57 (Box-folder 54/23)
    - Hilger and Busenburg, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 58 (Box-folder 54/24)
    - Coburn, Robert, Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 60 (Box-folder 54/25)
    - Riner and Schnitger, Cheyenne, Wyoming, Case Number 62 (Box-folder 54/26)
    - Renn, Adolph, Fallon, Montana, Case Number 64 (Box-folder 54/27)
    - Goddard, D. E., Lusk, Wyoming, Case Number 67 (Box-folder 54/28)
    - Missouri River Power Company, Helena, Montana, Case Number 68 (Box-folder 54/29)
    - Baker, Thomas T., Butte, Montana, Case Number 69 (Box-folder 54/30)
    - Bussett, J. D., Ritzville, Washington, Case Number 71 (Box-folder 54/31)
    - Day, J. S., Culbertson, Montana, Case Number 72 (Box-folder 54/32)
    - Lonabaugh and Wenzel, Sheridan, Wyoming, Case Number 75 (Box-folder 54/33)
    - Wunderlin, Joseph T., Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 76 (Box-folder 54/34)
    - Prescott, A. K., Helena, Montana, Case Number 78 (Box-folder 54/35)
    - Birkin, W. J., Billings, Montana, Case Number 80 (Box-folder 54/36)
    - Flowerree, William K., Lowrey, Montana, Case Number 82 (Box-folder 54/37)
    - Graham, Donald, Conrad, Montana, Case Number 84 (Box-folder 54/38)
    - Kalispell Lumber Company, Kalispell, Montana, Case Number 86 (Box-folder 54/39)
    - Connolly, Michael, Shelby, Montana, Case Number 93 (Box-folder 55/1)
    - Wasesha, Martin, Beatrice, Montana, Case Number 95 (Box-folder 55/2)
    - Flagler, Thomas, Fort Benton, Montana, Case Number 96 (Box-folder 55/3)
    - Morton, John S., Fort Benton, Montana, Case Number 97 (Box-folder 55/4)
    - Mills, L. H., Saco, Montana, Case Number 100 (Box-folder 55/5)
    - Walsh, Thomas J., Helena, Montana, Case Number 103 (Box-folder 55/6)
    - Preuitt, W. G. and Stadler and Kaufman, Helena, Montana, Case Number 104 (Box-folder 55/7)
    - Cruse, Thomas, Helena, Montana, Case Number 108 (Box-folder 55/8)
    - Crouch, Charles D., Helena, Montana, Case Number 110 (Box-folder 55/9)
    - C. B. Towers Company, Miles City, Montana, Case Number 226 (Box-folder 55/10)
    - Sieben, Henry, Helena, Montana, Case Number 227 (Box-folder 55/11)
    - Johnston, Charles A., Reynolds, Idaho, Case Number 228 (Box-folder 55/12)
    - Reynolds, C. B., Kalispell, Montana, Case Number 230 (Box-folder 55/13)
    - Godfrey, Otis Billings, Montana, Case Number 231 (Box-folder 55/14)
    - Tiffany, B. C., Case Number 232 (Box-folder 55/15)
    - Cage, Milton G., Boise, Idaho, Case Number 233 (Box-folder 55/16)
    - Miller, John J., Shelby, Montana, Case Number 234 (Box-folder 55/17)
    - Cage, Milton G., Boise, Idaho, Case Number 235 (Box-folder 55/18)
    - Sprague, Robert H., Lyon, Montana, Case Number 236 (Box-folder 55/19)
    - Jacobson and Reif, Chester, Montana, Case Number 237 (Box-folder 55/20)
    - Frary, W. S., Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 238 (Box-folder 55/21)
    - Citizens State Bank, Culbertson, Montana, Case Number 239 (Box-folder 55/22)
    - Magone, D. D., Thompson, Montana, Case Number 241 (Box-folder 55/23)
    - Moulton, C. E., Portland, Oregon, Case Number 242 (Box-folder 55/24)
    - Tolman, J. N., Red Lodge, Montana, Case Number 247 (Box-folder 55/25)
    - Hershey, Elmer E., Missoula, Montana, Case Number 250 (Box-folder 55/26)
    - Jones, George, Malta, Montana, Case Number 252 (Box-folder 55/27)
    - Child, Harry W., Helena, Montana, Case Number 253 (Box-folder 55/28)
    - Wood Livestock Company, Spencer, Montana, Case Number 261 (Box-folder 56/1)
    - Heinze, F. Augustus, Butte, Montana, Case Number 264 (Box-folder 56/2)
    - Dunleavy, A. S., Canton, Montana, Case Number 266 (Box-folder 56/3)
    - State Bank of Dillon, Dillon, Montana, Case Number 267 (Box-folder 56/4)
    - Boardman, John M., Helena, Montana, Case Number 268 (Box-folder 56/5)
    - Boardman, John M., Helena, Montana, Case Number 269 (Box-folder 56/6)
    - Murphy, John T., Helena, Montana, Case Number 270 (Box-folder 56/7)
    - Clark, E. M., Red Lodge, Montana, Case Number 275 (Box-folder 56/8)
    - Hilger and Busenburg and S.D. Robson, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 276 (Box-folder 56/9)
    - Kendrick, John B., Sheridan, Wyoming, Case Number 278 (Box-folder 56/10)
    - Mills, L. H., Saco, Montana, Case Number 279 (Box-folder 56/11)
    - Bassett, J. D., Ritzville, Washington, Case Number 280 (Box-folder 56/12)
    - Moss, Preston B., Billings, Montana, Case Number 281 (Box-folder 56/13)
    - Cruse, Thomas, Helena, Montana, Case Number 283 (Box-folder 56/14)
    - Cameron, Walter S., Stacy, Montana, Case Number 285 (Box-folder 56/15)
    - Kendrick, John B., Sheridan, Wyoming, Case Number 287 (Box-folder 56/16)
    - Selway, T. M., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 288 (Box-folder 56/17)
    - Stark, Leon B., Whitlash, Montana, Case Number 289 (Box-folder 56/18)
    - Buan, John, Erickson, Montana, Case Number 290 (Box-folder 56/19)
    - Frary, W. S., Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 291 (Box-folder 57/1)
    - Smith, Pearl I., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 292 (Box-folder 57/2)
    - Hartt and Godfrey, Two Dot, Montana, Case Number 293 (Box-folder 57/3)
    - Mosher, Stephen W., Clemons, Montana, Case Number 294 (Box-folder 57/4)
    - Albright, William H., Albright, Montana, Case Number 295 (Box-folder 57/5)
    - Taylor, William H., Saco, Montana, Case Number 296 (Box-folder 57/6)
    - Helvey, J. D., Sheridan, Wyoming, Case Number 297 (Box-folder 57/7)
    - Sundin, Ernest, Rawlins, Wyoming, Case Number 300 (Box-folder 57/8)
    - Sundin, Ernest, Rawlins, Wyoming, Case Number 301 (Box-folder 57/9)
    - Harris, C. L., Billings, Montana, Case Number 302 (Box-folder 57/10)
    - Edminston, Archibald D., Billings, Montana, Case Number 303 (Box-folder 57/11)
    - Moss, Preston B., Billings, Montana, Case Number 305 (Box-folder 57/12)
    - Briggman, W. J., Cold Creek, Montana, Case Number 306 (Box-folder 57/13)
    - Davis, Andrew J., Butte, Montana, Case Number 307 (Box-folder 57/14)
    - Walsh, Thomas J., Helena, Montana, Case Number 308 (Box-folder 57/15)
    - Selway Sheep Company, Dillon, Montana, Case Number 309 (Box-folder 57/16)
    - Kessinger, George H., Washington Gulch, Montana, Case Number 310 (Box-folder 57/17)
    - Jones, W. A. Fleming, Las Cruces, New Mexico, Case Number 312 (Box-folder 57/18)
    - C. B. Towers Company, Miles City, Montana, Case Number 313 (Box-folder 57/19)
    - Jenney, Warren, Anaconda, Montana, Case Number 318 (Box-folder 57/20)
    - Armstrong, Flora E., Armstead, Montana, Case Number 320 (Box-folder 57/21)
    - Valleaux, Narcisse or T. C. Power and Brother Limited, Fort Benton, Montana, Case Number 321 (Box-folder 57/22)
    - Christian, Grand B., Augusta, Montana, Case Number 322 (Box-folder 58/1)
    - Davis, Andrew J., Butte, Montana, Case Number 323 (Box-folder 58/2)
    - Yegen Brothers, Billings, Montana, Case Number 325 (Box-folder 58/3)
    - Thurston, L. S., Stanford, Montana, Case Number 326 (Box-folder 58/4)
    - Norton and Lyons, Big Elk, Montana, Case Number 327 (Box-folder 58/5)
    - Harris, C. L., Billings, Montana, Case Number 328 (Box-folder 58/6)
    - Telstad, Ralph, Conrad, Montana, Case Number 329 (Box-folder 58/7)
    - Strode, Thomas P., Whitlash, Montana, Case Number 330 (Box-folder 58/8)
    - Fey, Jacob C. and Arthur A., Stearns, Montana, Case Number 331 (Box-folder 58/9)
    - Hilger Loan and Realty Company, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 332 (Box-folder 58/10)
    - Furst, John, Anaconda, Montana, Case Number 334 (Box-folder 58/11)
    - Lundquist, John, Culbertson, Montana, Case Number 335 (Box-folder 58/12)
    - Marsh, L. C., Shelby, Montana, Case Number 336 (Box-folder 58/13)
    - Mills, Jacob, Helena, Montana, Case Number 337 (Box-folder 58/14)
    - Calvin Investment Company, Miles City, Montana, Case Number 338 (Box-folder 58/15)
    - Anderson, Clifford H., Helena, Montana, Case Number 340 (Box-folder 58/16)
    - Hauck, John C., Helena, Montana, Case Number 341 (Box-folder 58/17)
    - Bassett, J. D., Ritzville, Washington, Case Number 342 (Box-folder 58/18)
    - Giltinan, H. J., Bercail, Montana, Case Number 346 (Box-folder 58/19)
    - Delatour, Samuel P., Lewellyn, Montana, Case Number 348 (Box-folder 58/20)
    - Conrad, C. E., Kalispell, Montana, Case Number 349 (Box-folder 58/21)
    - Cruse, Thomas, Helena, Montana, Case Number 351 (Box-folder 59/1)
    - Wood Livestock Company, Spencer, Idaho, Case Number 353 (Box-folder 59/2)
    - Horkan, George, Miles City, Montana, Case Number 355 (Box-folder 59/3)
    - Kennedy, Lewis W., Saco, Montana, Case Number 360 (Box-folder 59/4)
    - Swank, Wesley T., Nashua, Montana, Case Number 363 (Box-folder 59/5)
    - LaDue, A. D., Luverne, Minnesota, Case Number 369 (Box-folder 59/6)
    - Redwater Land and Livestock Company, Helena, Montana, Case Number 370 (Box-folder 59/7)
    - Neill, John S. M., Helena, Montana, Case Number 373 (Box-folder 59/8)
    - Lawrence, John A., Dewey, Montana, Case Number 374 (Box-folder 59/9)
    - Blackfoot Cattle Company, Helena, Montana, Case Number 375 (Box-folder 59/10)
    - Hiram H. Babcock, (administrator of John Booker), Case Number 375 (Box-folder 59/11)
    - Smith, Arcelia, White Sulphur Springs, Montana, Case Number 376 (Box-folder 59/12)
    - Manley, John E., Drummond, Montana, Case Number 377 (Box-folder 59/13)
    - Stevens, George H., Fort Benton, Montana, Case Number 378 (Box-folder 59/14)
    - Benton, C. H. (for L. C. Marsh), Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 379 (Box-folder 59/15)
    - Brassey and Stack, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 380 (Box-folder 59/16)
    - Hilger and Busenburg, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 381 (Box-folder 59/17)
    - Brassey and Stack, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 382 (Box-folder 59/18)
    - Brassey and Stack, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 383 (Box-folder 59/19)
    - Shields, John W., Conrad, Montana, Case Number 385 (Box-folder 59/20)
    - Hill, H. B., Mondak, Montana, Case Number 388 (Box-folder 59/21)
    - Davis, John E., Butte, Montana, Case Number 389 (Box-folder 59/22)
    - Brassey and Stack, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 390 (Box-folder 59/23)
    - Sawyer and Austin Lumber Company, Pine Bluff, Arkansas, Case Number 391 (Box-folder 60/1)
    - Boardman, John M., Helena, Montana, Case Number 392 (Box-folder 60/2)
    - Yegen Brothers, Billings, Montana, Case Number 393 (Box-folder 60/3)
    - Brassey and Stack, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 394 (Box-folder 60/4)
    - Darling, M. S., Conrad, Montana, Case Number 395 (Box-folder 60/5)
    - Riba, A., Plentywood, Montana, Case Number 396 (Box-folder 60/6)
    - Hill, H. B., Mondak, Montana, Case Number 397 (Box-folder 60/7)
    - Gunn, M. S., Helena, Montana, Case Number 398 (Box-folder 60/8)
    - Hill, H. B. (for Margaret A. Hood), Mondak, Montana, Case Number 399 (Box-folder 60/9)
    - Brassey and Stack, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 404 (Box-folder 60/10)
    - Evans, H. R., Malad, Idaho, Case Number 406 (Box-folder 60/11)
    - Blackfoot Cattle Company, Helena, Montana, Case Number 407 (Box-folder 60/12)
    - Jones, John M., Anaconda, Montana, Case Number 408 (Box-folder 60/13)
    - Sweetman, L. D., Mondak, Montana, Case Number 411 (Box-folder 60/14)
    - Neill, John S. M., Helena, Montana, Case Number 427 (Box-folder 60/15)
    - Young, Robert F., Helena, Montana, Case Number 428 (Box-folder 60/16)
    - Pritchard, William, Gold Butte, Montana, Case Number 429 (Box-folder 60/17)
    - Loud and Hitzfeldt, Philbrick, Freeman, Miles City, Montana, Case Number 432 (Box-folder 60/18)
    - Hill and Griggs, Buffalo, Wyoming, Case Number 438 (Box-folder 60/19)
    - Haley, J. B., Terry, Montana, Case Number 440 (Box-folder 61/1)
    - Homestead Land Company, Chester, Montana, Case Number 441 (Box-folder 61/2)
    - Olson, Andrew, Poplar, Montana, Case Number 444 (Box-folder 61/3)
    - Gridley, C. E., Hagerman, Idaho, Case Number 449 (Box-folder 61/4)
    - Day, W. T., Spokane, Washington, Case Number 450 (Box-folder 61/5)
    - Marsh, L. C., Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 459 (Box-folder 61/6)
    - Steele, J. B., Three Creek, Idaho, Case Number 461 (Box-folder 61/7)
    - Day and Hansen Security Company, Spokane, Washington, Case Number 462 (Box-folder 61/8)
    - St. John, Carroll C., Birney, Montana, Case Number 463 (Box-folder 61/9)
    - Hubbell, L. W., Springfield, Missouri, Case Number 469 (Box-folder 61/10)
    - Shelton, John A., Butte, Montana, Case Number 471 (Box-folder 61/11)
    - Morris, C. F. (for Dr. J. A. Wright), Havre, Montana, Case Number 478 (Box-folder 61/12)
    - Victory Land and Investment Company (Albert Goeddertz, Jr.), Kevin, Montana, Case Number 480 (Box-folder 61/13)
    - Tolman, John N., Red Lodge, Montana, Case Number 481 (Box-folder 62/1)
    - Kreuger, Augustus H. W., Fulton, Montana, Case Number 489 (Box-folder 62/2)
    - Bailey, Benjamin J., Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 492 (Box-folder 62/3)
    - W. E. Moses Land Scrip and Realty Company, Denver, Colorado, Case Number 493 (Box-folder 62/4)
    - Miller, Mrs. Emma, Martinsdale, Montana, Case Number 498 (Box-folder 62/5)
    - W. C. Gillette Company, Craig, Montana, Case Number 499 (Box-folder 62/6)
    - Thompson, John, Camp Crook, South Dakota, Case Number 505 (Box-folder 62/7)
    - Bower, J. E., Helena, Montana, Case Number 513 (Box-folder 62/8)
    - Ramer, J. A., Miles City, Montana, Case Number 516 (Box-folder 62/9)
    - Stillman, C. N., Big Timber, Montana, Case Number 530 (Box-folder 62/10)
    - Garrard, William, Decker, Montana, Case Number 540 (Box-folder 62/11)
    - McVay, Thomas, Decker, Montana, Case Number 541 (Box-folder 62/12)
    - Riverside Land and Livestock Company, Helena, Montana, Case Number 543 (Box-folder 62/13)
    - Sieben, Henry, Helena, Montana, Case Number 548 (Box-folder 62/14)
    - Conrad National Bank, Kalispell, Montana, Case Number 561 (Box-folder 62/15)
    - McLeish, Arthur E., Fort Benton, Montana, Case Number 564 (Box-folder 62/16)
    - Harris, W. E., Miles City, Montana, Case Number 566 (Box-folder 63/1)
    - Boyle, Charles H., Fort Benton, Montana, Case Number 567 (Box-folder 63/2)
    - Harris, W. E., Miles City, Montana, Case Number 569 (Box-folder 63/3)
    - Hilger and Busenburg, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 570 (Box-folder 63/4)
    - Farr, George W., Miles City, Montana, Case Number 578 (Box-folder 63/5)
    - Neill, John S. M., Miles City, Montana, Case Number 579 (Box-folder 63/6)
    - Billings Land and Irrigation Company, Billings, Montana, Case Number 584 (Box-folder 63/7)
    - Bennett, Alvin, Buffalo, Wyoming, Case Number 594 (Box-folder 63/8)
    - Farady, C. B., Boise, Idaho, Case Number 603 (Box-folder 63/9)
    - Power, Charles B., Helena, Montana, Case Number 625 (Box-folder 63/10)
    - Brady, S. O., Myersburg, Montana, Case Number 628 (Box-folder 63/11)
    - Brockway, B. W., Malta, Montana, Case Number 629 (Box-folder 63/12)
    - Kendrick, John B., Sheridan, Wyoming, Case Number 641 (Box-folder 63/13)
    - Usher, L. J., Augusta, Montana, Case Number 656 (Box-folder 63/14)
    - Spencer, W. R., Malta, Montana, Case Number 667 (Box-folder 64/1)
    - Conrad Townsite Company, Conrad, Montana, Case Number 722 (Box-folder 64/2)
    - Simero, F. W., West Butte, Montana, Case Number 769 (Box-folder 64/3)
    - Strode, A. C., Whitlash, Montana, Case Number 790 (Box-folder 64/4)
    - Gunn, M. S., Helena, Montana, Case Number 851 (Box-folder 64/5)
    - Tolley, E. C., Joplin, Montana, Case Number 869 (Box-folder 64/6)
    - Phelps, L. G., Meeteetse, Wyoming, Case Number 876 (Box-folder 64/7)
    - American Livestock and Loan Company, Denver, Colorado, Case Number 889 (Box-folder 64/8)
    - Bennett, William M., New York City, New York, Case Number 890 (Box-folder 64/9)
    - Kuhn, Henry C., Cleveland, Montana, Case Number 893 (Box-folder 64/10)
    - Stadler and Kaufman, Helena, Montana, Case Number 894 (Box-folder 64/11)
    - Milner, M. E., Fort Benton, Montana, Case Number 932 (Box-folder 64/12)
    - Noblitt, J. D., Cokeville, Wyoming, Case Number 944 (Box-folder 64/13)
    - Quaintance, A. C., Boulder, Montana, Case Number 955 (Box-folder 64/14)
    - Jensen, Walter A., Joplin, Montana, Case Number 971 (Box-folder 64/15)
    - McNamara, Cornelius J., Helena, Montana, Case Number 989 (Box-folder 64/16)
    - Benton, C. H. (for L. C. Marsh), Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 993 (Box-folder 65/1)
    - Cage, Milton G., Boise, Idaho, Case Number 994 (Box-folder 65/2)
    - Hudson Land Company, The Dalles, Oregon, Case Number 997 (Box-folder 65/3)
    - Wood Livestock Company, Spencer, Idaho, Case Number 999 (Box-folder 65/4)
    - Jones, Edward, Conrad, Montana, Case Number 1000 (Box-folder 65/5)
    - Lambert, F. B., Minot, North Dakota, Case Number 1001 (Box-folder 65/6)
    - Moulton, C. E., Portland, Oregon, Case Number 1002 (Box-folder 65/7)
    - Day, J. S., Culbertson, Montana, Case Number 1003 (Box-folder 65/8)
    - Frary, W. S., Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 1004 (Box-folder 65/9)
    - Rines and Schnitger, Cheyenne, Wyoming, Case Number 1006 (Box-folder 65/10)
    - Flowerree, W. K., Lowry, Montana, Case Number 1008 (Box-folder 65/11)
    - Toman, Edward M., Cascade, Montana, Case Number 1009 (Box-folder 65/12)
    - Day, Joshua S., Culbertson, Montana, Case Number 1015 (Box-folder 65/13)
    - Dugal, Louis, Denver, Colorado, Case Number 1018 (Box-folder 65/14)
    - Lindquist, Frank W., Helena, Montana, Case Number 1019 (Box-folder 65/15)
    - Hays, Luke C., Harlem, Montana, Case Number 1027 (Box-folder 65/16)
    - Swenson, J. A., Thermopolis, Wyoming, Case Number 1028 (Box-folder 65/17)
    - Nutter, Preston, Utah, Case Number 1029 (Box-folder 65/18)
    - Woods, Charles E., Miles City, Montana, Case Number 1033 (Box-folder 65/19)
    - Gardner, Annie, Concord, Montana, Case Number 1034 (Box-folder 65/20)
    - Milner, M. E., Fort Benton, Montana, Case Number 1035 (Box-folder 66/1)
    - Helena Power and Transportation Company, Case Number 1036 (Box-folder 66/2)
    - Slayton, Dalton F., Billings, Montana; Hilger and Busenburg, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 1038 (Box-folder 66/3)
    - Hudson and Brownhill, The Dalles, Oregon, Case Number 1039 (Box-folder 66/4)
    - Denecke, W. A., Casper, Wyoming, Case Number 1041 (Box-folder 66/5)
    - Poindexter, J. B., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 1042 (Box-folder 66/6)
    - Hobson, J. S., Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 1046 (Box-folder 66/7)
    - Woods, William H., Red Lodge, Montana, Case Number 1047 (Box-folder 66/8)
    - Washburn, Jed. L., Red Lodge, Montana, Case Number 1050 (Box-folder 66/9)
    - Washburn, Jed. L., Red Lodge, Montana, Case Number 1051 (Box-folder 66/10)
    - Cardwell, Edward, Jefferson Island, Montana, Case Number 1052 (Box-folder 66/11)
    - Hitzfeldt, Fred, Miles City, Montana, Case Number 1053 (Box-folder 66/12)
    - Watson, C. R., Rawlins, Wyoming, Case Number 1056 (Box-folder 66/13)
    - Cruse, Thomas, Helena, Montana, Case Number 1057 (Box-folder 66/14)
    - Pacific Northwest Mining Corporation, Libby, Montana, Case Number 1058 (Box-folder 66/15)
    - Cobban, R. M., Missoula, Montana, Case Number 1059 (Box-folder 66/16)
    - O'Connor, John E., Canton, Montana, Case Number 1061 (Box-folder 66/17)
    - McDonough, J. A., Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 1063 (Box-folder 66/18)
    - Brassey and Shafer, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 1064 (Box-folder 67/1)
    - Medley, James W., Magdalene, New Mexico, Case Number 1065 (Box-folder 67/2)
    - Brassey and Shafer, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 1067 (Box-folder 67/3)
    - Skillman, C. N., Big Timber, Montana, Case Number 1068 (Box-folder 67/4)
    - Briggs-Ellis Company, Big Timber, Montana, Case Number 1070 (Box-folder 67/5)
    - Kendrick, John B., Sheridan, Wyoming, Case Number 1071 (Box-folder 67/6)
    - Fogarty, Edward, Sand Cliffs, Montana, Case Number 1075 (Box-folder 67/7)
    - Kendrick, John B., Sheridan, Wyoming, Case Number 1076 (Box-folder 67/8)
    - Noblitt, J. D., Cokeville, Wyoming, Case Number 1078 (Box-folder 67/9)
    - Clark, E. M., Clark, Wyoming, Case Number 1080 (Box-folder 67/10)
    - J. B. Long and Company, Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 1081 (Box-folder 67/11)